Class of 1937 Records, 1933-2002
Smith College Archives
Class of 1937 Records
1933-2002
Smith College. Class of 1937.
RG 80
10 boxes (5.2 linear ft.)
Smith College Archives Northampton, MA
This collection contains photographs, invitations, songs, newspaper clippings, and other memorabilia from the commencement and reunions of the Class of 1937.
Historical Note
The Class of 1937 was the fifty-ninth graduating class of Smith College.
Scope and Contents of the Collection
The Class of 1937 Records contain materials describing the history and activities of the Class of 1937, including materials from commencement activities, reunions, and other important events. Types of materials include photographs, invitations, songs, newspaper clippings, questionnaires, letters, financial records, and other memorabilia.
Individual biographical files are also available, and often include photographs, photo albums, newspaper clippings, letters and correspondences, and class notes.
Information on Use
Terms of Access and Use
The records are open for research according to the regulations of the Smith College Archives without any additional restrictions.
History of the Collection
The Class of 1937 Records were created by the students and donated to the College Archives.
- Clippings 1937 (Box 2100, Folder 1)
- Commencement 1937 (Box 2100, Folder 2)
- Commencement Dramatics 1937 (Box 2100, Folder 3)
- Commencement Music 1937 (Box 2100, Folder 4)
- Commencement Photographs 1937 (Box 2100, Folder 5)
- Commencement Speaker 1937 (Box 2100, Folder 6)
- First Chapel 1933 (Box 2100, Folder 7)
- Freshman Handbook 1933-1934 (Box 2100, Folder 8)
- Groups 1933-1937 (Box 2100, Folder 9)
- Smith Girl's Guide Book 1936-1937 (Box 2100, Folder 10)
- History 1933-1937 (Box 2100, Folder 11)
- History 1972 (Box 2100, Folder 12)
- Hoop Rolling 1937 (Box 2100, Folder 13)
- Ivy Day 1937 (Box 2101, Folder 1)
- Ivy Day-Photographs 1937 (Box 2101, Folder 2)
- Junior Prom 1936 (Box 2101, Folder 3)
- Junior Prom-Garden Party 1936 (Box 2101, Folder 4)
- Junior Ushers 1936 (Box 2101, Folder 5)
- Last Chapel 1937 (Box 2101, Folder 6)
- Class Letters 1956-2002 (Box 2101, Folder 7)
- Class Officers 1934 (Box 2101, Folder 8)
- Organization 1933 (Box 2101, Folder 9)
- Reunions 1938 (Box 2101, Folder 10)
- Reunions 1942 (Box 2101, Folder 11)
- Reunions 1947 (Box 2101, Folder 12)
- Reunions 1952 (Box 2101, Folder 13)
- Reunions 1957 (Box 2101, Folder 14)
- Reunions-Questionnaire 1957 (Box 2101, Folder 15)
- Reunions-"A Myoptic Report" 1957 (Box 2101, Folder 16)
- Reunions 1962 (Box 2101, Folder 17)
- Reunions 1967 (Box 2101, Folder 18)
- Reunions 1972 (Box 2101, Folder 19)
- Reunions 1977-1982 (Box 2101, Folder 20)
- Reunions 1987-1992 (Box 2101, Folder 21)
- Reunions-Songs 1972-1987 (Box 2101, Folder 22)
- Senior Questionnaire 1937 (Box 2101, Folder 23)
- Songs n.d. (Box 2101, Folder 24)
- Sophomore Carnival 1935 (Box 2101, Folder 25)
- Sophomore Push Committee 1935 (Box 2101, Folder 26)
- Step Sings 1937 (Box 2101, Folder 27)
- Class Supper 1937 (Box 2101, Folder 28)
- Treasurer 1933-1937 (Box 2101, Folder 29)
- Year Book 1936-1937 (Box 2101, Folder 30)
- Class Scrapbook (Box OV)